Breakthrough: Tufts' Undergraduate Science Magazine UP260
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Breakthrough: Tufts' Undergraduate Science Magazine
2009 -- 2019
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life
UP260
0.5 Linear Feet
1 Web sites
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Breakthrough: Tufts' Undergraduate Science Magazine and Web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Breakthrough and web crawls documenting its presence on the web. It is a publication of the Tufts Undergraduate Research Journal, recognized by the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Judiciary and funded by the TCU Senate. Publication began in Winter 2009-2010. Published each semester.
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the pervue of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
- Breakthrough: Tufts' Undergraduate Science Magazine, 2009 -- 2015; UP260.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Breakthrough. It is a publication of the Tufts Undergraduate Research Journal, recognized by the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Judiciary and funded by the TCU Senate. Publication began in Winter 2009-2010. Published each semester.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Breakthrough, Winter, 2009 -- 2010; UP260.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Tufts' undergraduate science magazine, Volume 1, Issue 1, Winter 2009-2010. http://www.tuftsroundtable.org/breakthrough Breakthrough: Tufts undergraduate Science Magazine is Tufts' first and only undergraduate magazine focused on the physical and natural sciences. Our goal is to describe scientific research and innovations in a way that is interesting to science majors and accessible to non-science majors, fostering cross-departmental discussion about science developments at Tufts and the world at large. In conjunction with the Tufts Roundtable.
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - Breakthrough, Spring, 2010; UP260.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    Breakthrough is a publication of the Tufts Undergraduate Research Journal, recognized by the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Judiciary and funded by the TCU Senate.
    1, 2
  - Breakthrough, Fall, 2010; UP260.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    II, 1
  - Breakthrough, Spring, 2011; UP260.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    II, 2
  - Breakthrough, Fall, 2011; UP260.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    III, 1
  - Breakthrough, Spring, 2012; UP260.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    III, 2
  - Breakthrough, Fall, 2013; UP260.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    IV, 1
  - Breakthrough, Spring, 2014; UP260.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    IV, 2
  - Breakthrough, Fall, 2014; UP260.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Breakthrough, Spring, 2015; UP260.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    V, 2
  - Breakthrough, Spring, 2015; UP260.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    V, 3
    publication
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2019; UP260.002; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Breakthrough: Tufts Undergraduate Science Magazine website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Breakthrough: Tufts Undergraduate Science Magazine, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-11-15; UP260.002.00001